It's me, Eden.
I saved you in the storm that day.
Again.
It's me, Eden.
I saved you in the storm that day.
Again.
As I've said before,
Luka's tone should be anxious, not certain.
Why don't we stay and practice this part a bit more?
Director Jung,
We can practice here all night, right?
Suit yourselves.
Guys!
We have a problem!
So your so-called problem...
Is that you're craving grilled meat so much...
This is the problem
You meant?
Hey, flip the meat! It'll burn.
Hurry.
I flip it?
Give it to me.
Wait, how are you so good at grilling?
I've worked part-time a lot.
Hey, see?
I'm an expert at picking people.
I'm a person too, okay?
Come on.
Let's all
Toast to "The Mermaid Prince."
Cheers!
Am I late?
Oh, Lawyer Yoo, you're here.
How've you been?
Great, of course.
The atmosphere is nice.
Right?
It's rare for everyone to be here.
Stop drinking.
I'm fine.
I'll drink it.
What for?
What's going on with them?
Quiet.
Right, of course
We have to down the first shot.
Everyone, raise your glasses.
Cheers!
Let me pour you a glass.
Sure, I'll have a glass.
[Hongseok]
[Park Seonghyeon]
[Shin Yongseok] [Shin Junseop] [Ha Yosep]
[Play Me]
Wait a minute.
Yeah, hello?
Uh-huh.
Okay, got it. Okay.
Yihyun.
Yeah?
Something urgent came up. I have to go.
Take care.
Oh, it's a taxi!
Hey!
I won!
That damn skyscraper...
I beat him.
I almost drank myself to death.
It's impossible to get a taxi.
Yihyun.
Don't hate me.
Don't push me away, please.
What?
This isn't my place.
Good morning.
Oh, I took your phone to get it repaired.
My phone?
Why?
I dropped it and it broke.
Don't you remember?
My phone's broken?
Hey!
Give me a ride. Right now.
Sorry!
I'm really sorry I'm late.
No matter how long it takes, I'll finish it before I leave.
You can count on me.
Well, just help me prep these fabrics.
Oh, okay.
By the way, wasn't there supposed to be another person coming today?
Since you didn't show up, I told them not to come.
So... I have to do all of this by myself?
Didn't you say I could count on you?
I'll leave it to you.
How can I finish all this by myself?
Is this how you wear it?
So cute... No,
It really suits you.
Yes, it suits you.
I really don't know why I have to help you.
That's irresponsible of you to say.
Who broke my phone?
Who took in a drunk person when they couldn't find their way home?
As they say, many hands make light work.
Take this...
Brush it out like this.
Hey, hey. What are you doing?
You cheeky thing.
Are you out of your mind?
We drifted apart because of this before, and now again.
We're going to drift apart again.
Just now...
Uh, I'm sorry.
No, what I mean is...
Uh, I drank a lot yesterday.
And... Oh.
I'm also a bit dizzy from the paint fumes, so...
Kang Jae-on.
I like you.
I said, I like you.
What'd you say?
It means what it means.
Um, so,
What... what is it that you mean?
What'd you say?
Didn't he tell me not to push him away?
That's why I didn't.
Since we kissed, I can't say I hate him.
So I said I like him.
What if he also says he likes me?
Fine.
Sure.
We're official from today.
Hey...
Let's pretend yesterday never happened.
Okay!
Huh?
[Epilogue]
I said, I like you.
All... All I view?
All I knew?
What is it that he knew?
View... What he views of our kiss?
But if I ask him again,
We'll probably drift apart again.
All...